This is a brand new song that I wrote really recently, like less than a couple of weeks ago
while I was in Melbourne, and I hope you enjoy it.
You tell me that you love me
When I'm lying by your side
You tell me that I am the only one
Who understands your troubled mind
That I am blind to any evil you could do
And that I love you more than any other girl could ever do
You love the things that I love
You love art and you love books
And you love love as much as I do
And you love my dirty looks Sing you love me right now So how can you love Vegemite
It tastes like sadness
It tastes like batteries
It tastes like asses
I cannot hold a man so close
Who spreads this cancer on his toast
It is the Vegemite
My darling, or it's me
You have to make a fucking choice
I cannot sit with you at breakfast
The very smell of it obliterates my senses
And if that weren't bad enough
You also eat the shit for lunch, which means we can't spend any time together.
What kind of relationship is that?
The choice is yours.
My heart is in your hands Please wash your hands You just ate Vegemite for lunch you selfish bastard It all about you isn it It just take take take take What about me What about my feelings
I'm sorry.
I had this really awful experience when I was six years old and our British next door neighbour, Christopher Gill,
Christopher Gill, he was babysitting us and he made me eat an entire spoonful of Marmite,
which is just like Vegemite pretty much, except it's even grosser.
And but he told me he made me eat it by telling me that it was chocolate fudge.
And so I swallowed the whole thing and then I had to go to the bathroom and throw up and
it really traumatized me.
And I'm sorry I got so emotional.
I just...
I love you.
And no matter what you eat, I'll always love you completely.
I might just always leave the room at mealtimes,
or refuse to kiss or touch you for a week If you insist on putting that foul death paste in your mouth You in my heart
Put yourself inside my shoes
I have to know
It shouldn't be too hard to choose
I know it's tearing you apart
But it's the way it has to be
It is the Vegemite, my darling
Put down the Vegemite, you fucker
Or I'll leave
Thank you.